[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
We have the same scent.
I like this.
I don't want
to be friends with you anymore.
I want to date you.
Nothing will change.
You'll live your life as usual.
Eat, sleep,
and go to school
when you need to.
Tell me when there's something funny.
Get angry when something bothers you.
If you're angry,
just tell me.
But
be it summer or winter, stay with me.
Don't avoid me again.
One week.
One week?
Let's date for a week first.
I told you not to avoid me.
Yet you found a way out.
I mean... What if we find it better
to be friends after starting to date?
We've been friends for 19 years,
so let's date for 19 years.
If you think it isn't me,
let's talk about it then.
But you can't do that now.
You have no choice.
Hey.
After dating for 19 years,
we'll be middle-aged uncles,
you crazy dude.
But in my eyes,
you'll always be pretty.
Where did you learn
to say things like that?
I learned it for this day. Why?
Stop it. It's ticklish.
It's ticklish?
I still find it difficult,
strange, and scary.
But as long as I'm with Cha Dohyun,
it seems like it'll be okay.
As for whether I call him
my friend or lover,
it doesn't matter anymore.
As long as it's him.
[Sung Inho]
[Kim Domin]
[Summertime]
[D-119]
All right, let me see what your dream is.
To be president?
You know what the president does, right?
The president is someone
who can do anything he wants.
Do you know how long
the president's term is?
I want to be a president
for about 20 years.
Hey.
Do you think it's the president
of some random football club?
I can go a rank lower.
How about a congressman?
That sounds not bad.
Do you think anyone
can be a congressman?
Well, as long as you have a loud voice,
and good at lying, no?
Seriously?
I wonder what you'll do when you grow up.
I want to make a lot of money.
That again.
Gunwoo...
I want to be a landlord.
I want to have 7 floors in Gangnam.
Why not 10 floors?
10 floors...
is a little too much.
Is there any difference?
Fine.
I want to be a rapper.
Are you cussing out at me now?
No.
Don't you know what gesture this is?
No, I don't.
Rappers do.
Okay, be careful with it in the future.
What about you, Yihyun?
I'm happy doing anything
but being a pastor.
Okay.
Okay, Yeo Eunho...
What?
You're okay with doing anything too?
I don't know what to choose.
You must have dreams.
I don't know.
Is there nothing you want to do?
No.
Don't you have anything you like?
Come in!
Here are the documents you asked for.
Okay, thank you.
Go ahead.
Well...
I heard you two grew up together.
Yes.
How long do you think
this friendship will last?
Going to different universities,
doing different jobs—
you'll have to grow up one day.
By then,
no matter it's friendship or not,
there will be different social circles
you hang out with.
Childhood friendship is useless.
So think about who you're friends with
and discuss with your parents
which university you want to enroll in.
Got it?
Okay.
[Cha Dohyun: good at studying,
student council president, handsome]
[Me: bad at studying, a proud
member of the school, handsome and cute]
[Cha Dohyun: can get into a good school]
[Me: can work at my parents']
[Cha Dohyun: can find a good job]
[Me: ??]
And then? What about dating?
[Dating? Marriage?]
What about marriage?
What would we be like then?
In 10 years,
will we still be childhood friends,
old friends,
[Will we be childhood friends,
old friends or lovers?]
or lovers?
You said you had no friends
other than me. Nonsense.
Are you crazy?
What if someone sees us?
So what?
Speaking of, where's everyone?
What's going on?
They went for lunch without me?
I asked them to go.
I can do that with my current identity.
What identity?
Let's go to the snack shop.
I'm hungry.
Okay.
By the way,
don't you have anything to do
for the student council today?
I was fired.
What?
No.
To be exact, I quit.
Why?
Because it's hard
to focus on studying and dating
while being the student council president,
so I quit.
Are you crazy?
What about plus points
for college applications?
The term of the student council president
is a semester.
When my term was up last week,
I handed it over.
Is that so?
Didn't you say we were going
to the snack shop?
[Teacher's Toilet]
Why are we here?
Hey!
[Occupied]
Are you crazy? We're in school.
You pervert!
Let me go!
Do you want the whole school
to know that you kissed?
Wait for me at the gate
after the festival.
Yeo Eunho.
Hey, I said we'd meet at the gate.
Why did you come out from here instead?
Stay back.
Go away.
Let's go home together.
No!
[Cha Dohyun]
What? He's still up?
Hello?
Are you upset?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Yeo Eunho, what are you doing?
Playing games.
Where?
On the bed.
What are you eating?
Short sleeves and undies.
My mom told me to save electricity
and not turn on the air conditioner.
It's so hot.
Are you angry because I ran away?
Actually, I let you go on purpose.
Then why are you calling me?
What game are you playing?
A racing game.
Darn it. Why did he throw that out
at the beginning?
Yeo Eunho.
Call my name.
Cha Dohyun.
One more time.
Cha Dohyun!
Hey!
Yeah?
What are you doing?
Thinking about you
listening to your voice.
So, while thinking about me
listening to my voice,
what are you doing?
Yeo Eunho.
Do you want to come to my house now?
You darn pervert. I'm hanging up.
If you don't come, I'll go to you.
See you in the central park.
What took you so long?
Thank you.
Hey.
Are you moving out for college?
Do you want me to do that?
Why are you asking me?
I'm asking if you want me
to move out after graduation.
I mean...
I'm just thinking if the school is far
it'd be tiring to commute.
Jihyun doesn't come home often anyway.
There's no need to stay there.
Is there a place you want to stay?
What?
It's convenient to stay near school,
but it's probably noisy around there too.
Why are you asking me?
If you don't really care,
I'll just decide.
What does that have to do with me?
After all, we're staying together.
I can't decide on my own.
I'm staying with you?
Do you want to live here alone then?
If there's somewhere you want to stay,
let me know.
I'll apply for a university near there.
Hey!
What are you talking about?
I'm just going to work odd jobs
in our neighborhood,
or go to the army early.
I was thinking if you moved out,
I'd go hang out with you
from time to time.
Why should I stay at your place?
If I don't live here,
how will this be our neighborhood?
Whether it's doing part-time jobs
or retaking the college entrance exams,
stay at my place.
Even if you refuse,
nothing will change in the end.
So just accept it.
How can I live alone
without you?
You're so annoying.
Saying you're going to apply
for a college around here...
Are you trying to say
you can get into any college you want?
Why ask the obvious?
Hey, why do you have this?
You threw it at me while running.
Wasn't it for me to see?
[Cha Dohyun: good at studying, student council president,
handsome, can get into a good school, can find a good job]
[Me: bad at studying, a proud member of the school,
handsome and cute, can work at my parents, live with Cha Dohyun]
[Childhood friends? Old friends? Lovers?]
[All of the above]
Don't worry, Eunho.
Kids,
the college entrance exam
is coming real soon.
Yes, I'm worried too.
Don't think you can fool around
during the vacation, okay?
Yes.
Who's on duty today?
Okay. Lock the windows and doors
before leaving.
That's it for this semester's
last weekly meeting.
Bye-bye!
Hey! Internet cafe?
Of course.
You guys are going too, right?
Yeah.
What about you?
My mom asked me to help at the store.
I have to go there early.
Come to see us when it's closed.
We'll stay up all night anyway.
Okay.
Is Sungho buying dinner tonight?
What are you talking about?
Nice!
You're here.
What? Why are you giving me this?
Today is our 7th day together.
You're right.
You said we'd date for 7 days—
saying we might be better off as friends.
So?
Do you know what yellow roses symbolize?
How would I know?
Friendship
and eternal love.
One flower has these two meanings.
It probably means these two identities
are similar.
Yeo Eunho.
Yeo Eunho, what's wrong?
You don't like these flowers?
Will you hold hands and kiss your friends?
I won't do that, you lunatic.
And I can't stand having friends
like that around you.
If you do, cut it off as soon as possible.
Also,
how can friendship and love be the same?
You fool.
[Summertime]
Hello, 20-year-old Yeo Eunho.
We're 20 now.
-A man's life... starts now!
-Starts now!
Damn you, Cha Dohyun!
I hope I never fight with Yeo Eunho,
and we stay happy forever.
How many times have I told you
to make a wish in your heart? Silly.
It won't come true if you say it out.
My wish
will come true.
Where's Cha Dohyun?
We broke up.